[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Law of Pythagoras can always be used to find the length of the hypotenuse of an isosceles triangle.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that in the movie High School Musical, Sharpay says she has acted in 17 school productions?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The General Grant tree in Kings Canyon National Park, USA, the only living object to be declared a National Shrine, is of what tree species?", "correct_answer": "Giant Sequoia", "incorrect_answers": ["American Beech", "Red Pine", "White Oak"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these regions is most affected by AIDS, as about 60% of all the HIV-infected people in the world live there?", "correct_answer": "Sub-Saharan Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Latin America", "East Asia", "Western Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these fruits is a an accessory fruit, just like strawberries?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Fig", "Cashew", "Pineapple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the USA, the color of the plastic tags, used to seal bread bags, indicates on what day the loaves were baked.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The term bibliobibuli refers to people who do what?", "correct_answer": "Read too much", "incorrect_answers": ["Use only recycled paper", "Use a lot of toilet paper", "Do not recycle paper"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael J. Fox waited for the TV show Family Ties to end before taking on Back to the Future.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Goonies Andi says Oh, I stubbed my toe.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "I would rather be a ghost drifting by your side as a condemned soul than enter heaven without you. Because of your love, I will never be a lonely spirit. (2000)", "correct_answer": "Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon", "incorrect_answers": ["Don Juan DeMarco", "Ever After", "Dracula"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was Triceratops first discovered?", "correct_answer": "1888", "incorrect_answers": ["1894", "1885", "1906"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "These small bodies are considered left overs from the formation of the Solar system some 4.6 billion years ago.", "correct_answer": "Asteroids", "incorrect_answers": ["Comets", "Stars", "Planets"]}]